I wonder where everyone meets
their soulmates.
I want a rich, handsome husband too.
The new season of Last Princess
is streaming!
All right, let’s watch it! Right now!
I'm in the mood for romance,
so we are watching this now!
I'm Kotaro Komiyama.
Through my hobby,
I've built up some muscles.
That's my charm.
This guy seems super shady.
Total meathead vibes.
I'm Airi.
I'm 27 years old. I work as a model.
Wow, she's gorgeous!
She's totally a pro at this romance stuff.
She's not all that.
-Wow, you're amazing!
-Not really.
Saunas are very trendy right now.
They are, they're super popular.
You're such a sharp businessman
to see opportunity in that!
There it is!
Those are staple lines of popular girls.
-"You're amazing!"
-"I didn't know that!"
-"Wow!"
-"You have great sense!"
"I see."
You two are amazing!
I went and got certified
as a food advisor!
-Really?
-Oh, she has qualifications.
So she's not like me.
I like people who are like aliens.
There it is, the quirky ditz persona.
When you can't win with a conventional
approach, you have to act weird.
Girls like her surprisingly
make it far in these shows.
I want to have a romance
like Last Princess too!
Who are you?
Mr. Konta invited us over!
Isn't this just like…
Our very own reality dating show?
-I've got to put on makeup.
-What?
-Me too!
-Huh? Wait… Well…
Please wait just a moment.
I have no choice but to win.
I am confident.
I'm betting my 27 years of life,
I will win this.
I want to be in a relationship
where we help each other grow.
And I will find it, no matter what.
Who will win and be chosen
as the last princess?
Okay…
Whoa. So much trash.
-Here.
-Thank you.
So, you all came here
because my brother invited you?
Yes. Wait, he's your brother?
Oh, right.
I'm Midori, Konta's younger sister.
I'm Rinrin, Midori's friend.
Likewise, I'm her friend, Tsumugi.
Sorry, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Kotaro.
They are my friends from college.
I'm Ryusei.
I'm Norito.
We came here from Tokyo.
We met Mr. Konta by chance
at a roadside station,
and he said, "We're having a barbecue
at my villa, you should come."
I see.
So, where is my brother?
He's still out buying groceries.
He said, "There are three ladies
at home, you can go there first."
Nice, Konta!
He can be useful sometimes.
You said you all came from Tokyo,
so what do you do for work?
I work at an IT company.
I'm a financial planner.
I run my own company.
They're handsome and successful!
Perhaps they are
our matches made in heaven?
Our inspirational Last Princess?
Our dating show has finally begun!
That's right.
I think I've been in more relationships
than the average girl.
But I think it's about time
I find that one special soulmate.
My type?
Let's see…
I think I like a man who can lead,
so I can always walk
three steps behind him.
I'm actually quite traditional.
RINRIN
#I WILL STOP BEING EVERYONE'S IDOL
I came here to experience
the passionate love of a lifetime.
WHAT KIND OF LOVE DO YOU WANT?
Let's see…
Whether you're my friend or not,
I don't plan on holding back.
TSUMUGI
#THE ROMANCE WRECKER WITH NOTHING TO LOSE
I'm currently unemployed.
But when it comes to housework
like cooking and cleaning,
I work harder than anyone!
MIDORI
#MY NEXT WORKPLACE IS Y-O-U!
FINALLY, A WORD ON YOUR RESOLVE
-I will…
-Definitely…
Find a good person here
and go back to Tokyo with him!
Well then,
here's to our wonderful meeting.
-Cheers!
Drinking at midday,
on a sunny day like this, is the best.
It really makes you feel free, doesn't it?
Mr. Kotaro, this is a bit sudden,
but can I take a photo
with you over there?
Sure.
Thank you.
Rinrin is amazing. She knows that
the first move is crucial in romance.
Right. We can't match her.
-Mr. Ryusei.
-What?
Care to share some wine
with me over there?
Seriously?
Sounds good.
Midori.
Romance is a survival game.
Were you always
this motivated about romance?
What do you do at your IT company?
I'm the CD for our product branch.
CD?
Do you mean a CD for listening to music?
Oh, wow!
She's doing the quirky ditz act!
No, that's not it.
It stands for "creative director."
Wow! Creative?
Your job must take a lot of talent!
I'm lucky my tastes are so well-received.
It's just luck.
-No, you're talented.
-Not at all.
The popular girls' staple lines…
She's making full use of them!
By the way, you look pretty well-built.
-You noticed?
-Yes.
Actually, I hit the gym four times a week.
Amazing! Do you also
pay close attention to your diet?
I do.
My diet basically revolves around
protein and lean meats.
I'm also quite health-conscious.
Lately, I even got
a food advisor certificate!
-Oh, really?
-Liar!
You just saw that on Last Princess!
I can make any dish!
You're a financial planner, right?
Yes. If you're interested,
I can help you with your life planning.
Thank you.
Then, in return,
I'll help you with your life planning.
What? Are you also a licensed FP?
No, I'm not certified, but…
I can see the future.
She's going for the eccentric act!
Can you explain?
I love fortune-telling.
I do tarot, and I can also read palms.
I see!
Let me borrow your right hand.
Casual physical contact…
Tsumugi, you are also
quite experienced in this, huh?
I've heard celebrities and successful
people often have a "charisma line."
Do I have it?
No, it doesn't look like
you have a charisma line.
However, your life line
is incredibly long.
Oh, and your head line is quite short.
Short?
Wait, do you even have it?
Maybe you don't.
-Can you cook anything?
-Oh, that's not it.
What kind of work do you do?
Oh.
I am not working right now.
A lot happened.
You're Mr. Konta's younger sister, right?
Yes.
I see! That explains it!
What? No, that's not it!
You see, unlike my brother,
I actually care about my future.
-It's okay, I understand.
-What?
-I'm the same way.
What kind of business
are you preparing to launch?
B-Business?
Well, I'm not sure about business.
In fact, I'm not even sure
what I want to do yet.
-Ms. Midori!
-What?
That is a dangerous way of thinking.
What?
If you think of business in terms of
what you want to do, you will fail!
No, but…
I don't plan to start a business.
What?
Oh, well…
How do I start, then?
First is surveying.
You survey various people
to identify insights before you set up.
There are so many entrepreneurs
who don't understand this.
That's why everyone fails.
I see. You're amazing, Mr. Norito.
Oh, if you would like,
I have a members-only service
where I post all about entrepreneurship.
Would you like to subscribe to my service?
A subscription?
Yes! You can learn business know-how
for just 550 yen a month.
It's a great deal.
Subscribe?
No, I won't.
I can't afford
to be wasting money right now.
I was thinking when I eventually
get married and have a family,
for the sake of my children,
I should acquire some knowledge
about food and cooking, starting now.
Wait, am I getting ahead of myself?
I'm sorry, did I talk too much?
No, it's just… too dazzling.
Oh, my…
I mean the sunlight.
What?
I really don't want to get a sunburn.
Could we swap seats?
Actually, should we just head inside?
Should we do that?
-Let's go inside.
-Yeah.
If you hate UV rays that much,
you should have worn sunscreen
before coming!
This painting
must be really expensive too.
That's true.
It's amazing, right?
Yes, it has a deep flavor.
A deep flavor?
All right!
So heavy.
I'm back!
-Are you a guest?
-Right.
He's our servant.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, hello.
Amazing.
What would you like to drink next?
I'm not sure…
Hey.
Do you have red? Red?
Red?
I mean red wine.
-Oh, red!
-Red wine. Yes, please.
Red…
-Oh, red!
-It's beautiful.
-It's a great size.
-That's right.
Red.
-The walls are pretty too.
-Yes, they are.
-They go well together.
-Yes.
Red!
Wait, no.
That's a lot.
Oh, wow.
Well then!
-Cheers.
This color…
I wonder if it's a Pinot Noir
from Burgundy.
Cherry…
Raspberry… It's so fruity.
RED WINE FOR COOKING USE
But the mouthfeel is soft.
SUPER CHEAP RED WINE FOR COOKING USE
Hey, this isn't bad.
I think if you decant it a bit more,
the aroma will open up even further.
Decant?
Decant. This.
-Decant.
-Decant!
That wine is a cooking wine
I bought from a nearby supermarket.
A 780-yen wine.
Was there anyone you liked?
Let's see… How should I put it?
It's not that they're bad people…
I get it.
It's like…
They are completely empty inside.
Exactly.
They sound smart when they talk,
but they feel weirdly shallow.
It seems they were classmates in college.
He gave me his socials.
Wow!
It feels like a seminar channel!
Well, it's not like
they're bad people, right?
I'm going to stick it out a little longer!
I've had enough.
Seminar guys
are not romantic options for me.
True.
When I talked to him,
he was all business talk.
What is up with that?
Would you like a refill?
Thank you.
By the way, do you all have girlfriends?
No, I don't.
-Me neither.
-Same here.
Oh! I thought girls
would be all over you guys!
No way.
I guess work is my girlfriend right now.
My marriage phase
is quite far in the future.
Hey, will Mr. Konta be back soon?
I got a message from him earlier.
He said he'll be here any minute.
I see! Great!
We came here
because we wanted to talk to him!
What?
Mr. Konta, the millionaire
who got to retire at a young age.
Say what?
What made you so interested in me?
I knew you were someone extraordinary!
Please teach us the secret
to your success, Mr. Konta.
How you became a millionaire
at a young age!
The three of us
actually post videos online.
Would you consider appearing in one?
Cheers!
No! The meat!
Today, I think I finally figured out
who I should really be looking at.
Would you be willing to invest in us?
1,000.
Sure.
Mr. Nishigami!
I am… Mr. Nishigami…
What?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.